e2language.com 2016-10-15

# E2Language - Privacy

This Privacy Policy provides you with information about how we collect, protect and use personal information as part of the normal operation of our services.

You may opt out of any use or disclosure by contacting us and notifying us of your choice.

 **Information we collect**

We collect personal information that can identify you such as Your facebook account, name and email address and other information that does not identify You. We also collect samples of your audio when you submit it for evaluation.

When you provide information through our application or website, the information will be sent to servers located in locations around the world.

 **Use of Your Information**

We use the information we collect to:

  * Deliver the services and products that you have requested
  * Manage your account and provide you with customer support
  * Enforce our terms and conditions
  * Manage our business
  * Perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection
  * Improve our software

 **Removing your information**

Upon notification, we will remove your information from our active databases as soon as reasonably possible in accordance with our policy and applicable law. Do note that removing your information can cause our application and services to stop functioning.

 **Disclosure of Your Information**

As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party.

 **Legal Requests**

We cooperate with law enforcement agencies and other third parties to enforce laws, as well as investigate and prosecute unlawful activities such as frauds and scams.

 **Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer or device for record keeping purposes. Cookies can take the form of application settings, session cookies or persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when you close your application or browser and is used to make it easier for you to navigate our application and website. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for specified period of time or permanently.

A cookie assists us in providing you with a better user experience by tracking your online activity on our application, such as the screens or web pages you visit, the buttons or links you click, and the searches you conduct. We may use a persistent cookie to assist with providing our services. You may delete cookies however If you do so, some of the features and services of our website may not function properly.

 **Information Others Collect**

In order to improve our application and website, we utilize web analytics software ("Software") to collect information about use of our application and website. This Software collects Users' information such as visiting frequency, screens and pages visited, and location. The Software also plants a permanent cookie to identify a user as unique. The Software identifies a user solely by the cookie in encrypted format, and does not identify a user by name or other personally identifiable information. We do not combine the information collected with other personally identifiable information.

 **Security**

To safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, E2Pronounce utilizes sophisticated security techniques and procedures, including: daily security and vulnerability scans, software audits, firewalls, and data encryption (Secure Socket Layers). E2Pronounce makes every effort to protect that data against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by others.

 **Note about Children**

Children under the age of 13 are required to get parental approval before using our application.

 **Modifications to Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is subject to change by us at any time based on changes in the law or our need to accurately reflect our data collection and disclosure practices. Changes are effective upon posting on the website.
